No Face to Wide Area Network 1.
We will now begin
full-scale combat operations.
All Legion within this network
are to cease standby operations.
Our targets are the Giad Federacy
in the eastern region,
the United Kingdom of Roa Gracia
to the north,
the Alliance of Wald to the south,
and the Republic of San Magnolia
to the west.
All Legion attached to this network,
begin the attack.
Wake up.
Listen...
At least say "wake up"
before you yank out my pillow.
There's no time.
They're finally coming?
Yeah.
August 28th, Stellar Year 2149
How many?
I don't want to even try to count.
If anything,
I wish somebody would tell me.
This isn't like you.
This is close to the worst case
I'd imagined.
Some of the forces I'd expected them to send
to other nations are headed for the Federacy.
The West appears to be the most
important theater to the Legion.
Well, ain't that an honor.
You...
During the battle today, don't connect to me
unless you absolutely have to.
I thought I was used to it,
but what I'm feeling tonight is rough.
Roger.
I'll let you get the unit prepared.
Wake the others.
What about you?
This isn't the time to stay quiet.
I'm waking up the entire army.
Shit. If this turns out to be a drill,
that so-called Reaper is gonna get
an "accidental" bullet to the back.
I'll shoot him where he stands.
You two wouldn't stand a chance.
Stop talking and get ready.
What?
Are those all...
There are so many!
Incoming fire for effect!
Defense Line 1 has taken heavy enemy damage!
Requesting reinforcements from the rear!
Everybody who's still alive,
gather up your weapons and ammo!
We're defending this place,
no matter what!
We've calculated the enemy's total numbers!
Displaying on monitor!
No... So every area in the theater
is under large-scale assault?
This is far more than we expected.
The western front is going to collapse!
The United Kingdom of Roa Gracia and the
Alliance of Wald are experiencing similar attacks.
They're both giving it their all,
but I don't know that they'll be able to last.
Ma'am.
Lieutenant Nouzen, what's the situation?
When will you be ready to go?
Whenever.
Nordlicht squadron is all ready to go.
How are you ready so fast?
You did not authorize us to prepare,
but please save any lectures for later.
All right. Tell me
all about this later, Lieutenant.
Maintain our combat lines until the other units
are ready to go, no matter the cost!
Roger.
Retreat!
The Löwes are coming!
Commander!
Don't go!
No one can save them now.
Follow me!
A Reginleif...
So this is Nordlicht squadron...
Are there any other survivors?
Not any more.
We're the last.
The others were all killed
by those scrapheads.
I see.
Withdraw and regroup, please.
We'll buy you time.
Okay... Let's get to work.
There they are!
Look at 'em all!
Like ants that had their nest kicked in.
I'll start with their commanders.
I'll be changing places, so back me up.
Roger, Kurena.
Leave the little ones to me.
Okay, here we go!
Don't shoot, Nordlicht squadron.
We're allies.
That headless skeleton...
You're the commander, right?
Lieutenant Shinei Nouzen,
commander of Nordlicht squadron.
What's the situation?
It appears we managed to drive off
the first wave of Legion attackers.
As have the other combat areas.
This happened only because your emergency unit
managed to hold them off.
You saved a lot of lives.
The other units have all launched.
It's okay now.
Fall back and resupply,
then follow orders from command.
The Federacy will handle this.
I'm sorry, but that last Legion unit
was just an advance force.
The second group is the main one.
If we fall back now,
this area will collapse.
What?
We'll leave this area to you.
We're going to intercept the main wave.
If we can take down the front line
of their advance, it will slow them down.
Wait, Lieutenant.
What do you mean—
Transmission over.
You all heard that, right?
Follow me if you want to live.
Right!
Take all the ammo we've got!
The minute a truck is full up, it goes!
Sergeant, our spares are ready to go!
Have them ready to go when ordered.
Yes, ma'am!
Listen to me!
Don't make Fido come get anything!
He needs to concentrate
on supporting the commander!
Bringing supplies to the front
when they're needed is our job!
Fire.
Looks like we're just getting started.
If only I knew where Kiri was,
I could help them...
There!
The second wave is being held off
in all combat areas!
Nordlicht squadron has begun advancing
on the enemy's main formation!
They're still fighting on the front lines!
They're monsters.
Shinei.
Shinei, Kiri is...
Are you listening, Shinei?
Kiri is...
What are you doing, Shinei?
Shinei...
Shinei!
No...
No!
Shin?
You...
You mustn't keep fighting like that!
Command to all members
of Nordlicht squadron.
Good work.
The Legion are falling back.
Return to base.
Roger.
Frederica?
Shinei, you fool.
You're just like Kiri.
You huge fool!
August 25th, Stellar Year 2149
This is Northern Combat Lines
Combat District 1 Squadron 1, Sledgehammer...
To all Eighty-Six Processors
hearing this message...
This is Sledgehammer Combat Commander, Blackbird.
Our war is over.
All Processors hearing this message...
All who fought to the end...
All who survived...
We're finally leaving the service.
We all did our best, huh?
You get what you deserve.
What's that?
A movie?
Somebody turn off that alarm!
Quiet!
The Gran Mur...
The railgun...
Lena, that warning!
I may as well let you know, Your Highness.
The main attack came from the north!
The north side's fallen,
and the east and west are under attack
from the north, too!
Yes, Annette, Cyclops.
I'm aware.
It's finally time.
What do you think
you're doing, Captain Milizé?
General Karlstahl...
I'm bringing all squadrons
from all areas inside the Gran Mur
to build a defense line
before the Legion reach District 1
and intercept the enemy there.
If we do that, we may still survive.
Forget it.
The people of the Republic would be better off
being destroyed by the Legion
than letting Eighty-Six inside the Gran Mur.
Are you still—
The Eighty-Six will never fight
for the Republic.
The Republic oppressed, abandoned,
and slaughtered them.
Even if we beg them to protect us now,
they have no reason or obligation to do so.
The most they'll do is laugh
and tell us we're getting what we deserve.
They aren't obligated, but they do have a reason.
We possess manufacturing and
power plants that they don't have.
They've spent enough time on the battlefield
that when it comes down to it,
they'll decide that
they need those things to survive.
They may obey us at first,
but they'll soon realize that it would be
much easier to fight the Legion alone
than protect a bunch of useless citizens
who do nothing but complain.
And what will happen then?
If we're lucky,
it will just be a massacre.
But you've studied enough history
to know that that won't be the case.
Even so...
I don't want to give up on everything
or just wait to die!
Even if I'm going to fail and die,
I want to fight
until that moment comes!
Otherwise...
The ones who did the same...
The ones who believed
that I could do the same...
I'll never be able to face them!
We have an explanation
regarding the warning a moment ago.
Soldiers and officers,
please come to the meeting hall.
I repeat:
We have an explanation
regarding the warning a moment ago.
Soldiers and officers,
please come to the meeting hall.
Then do what you want.
Follow your impossible dream
until you're satisfied.
It's a child's right to dream, Captain Milizé,
and until that child wakes up
from her dream
and is crushed against the rocks
of a merciless reality,
it's an adult's job to protect her.
I can buy you time, if nothing else.
Did you always intend to...
It's time for you to be crushed, Lena,
as you watch your naïve dreams
shatter against reality.
Wait, uncle—
Good luck, General Karlstahl.
I'm going to reach that place.
Para-RAID, activate.
Synchronization target:
All processors.
Synchronization complete.
Bloody Regina to all Processors
in all combat areas!
A large-scale Legion offensive has begun!
You are to gather within the 85 districts
and begin combat.
All personnel within National Defense HQ,
remove anti-personnel mines
and open the Gran Mur's gates immediately.
Everything we've done was for this day...
To protect our honor...
Let's fight until the end.
On that day,
Kiri attacked the Republic.
What I saw was a shattered wall
and a burning five-color flag.
And a huge Legion...
Which means?
They're inside the 85 districts?
It's probably all over then, right?
Yeah.
Is he still attacking the Republic?
No, now he's...
I'll kill you!
Get down! Kiri is...!
"I won't forget."